<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Yudan Ren on Virologist</title><link>https://yudanren.com/</link><description>Recent content in Yudan Ren on Virologist</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yudanren.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 023</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt23/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt23/</guid><description> For certain Biomedical research, it is true that who has the resource then who is going to publish more and more.
One could not see a virus without an electron microscope, one could not do virus qPCR testing without a PCR machine&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 022</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt22/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt22/</guid><description> Life in an avocado seed.</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 021</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt21/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt21/</guid><description> It is TT ball vs chopsticks today!</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 020</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt20/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt20/</guid><description> It was a sad day knowing someone is suffering from Cancer at the hospital.</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 019</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt19/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt19/</guid><description> Vyas Raina (CUTTC current Vice President) receiving from Professor Simon Maddrell.
Taken for the St. Catherine&amp;rsquo;s College TT Team winning the University League Division 1 in 1962.</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 018</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt18/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt18/</guid><description/></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 017</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt17/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt17/</guid><description> Bluebells!</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 016</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt16/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt16/</guid><description> What a beautiful tree in blossom!</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 015</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt15/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt15/</guid><description> Sunday morning at Cambridge was lovely and sunny. I took a pill for the hay fever and went out for a run.
Fancy to try the pre &amp;amp; post run exercise? Sit against the wall &amp;amp; tree for 3 mins.
It’s great to practise again: Stop worrying, get actions going, you will be there in no time.</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 014</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt14/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt14/</guid><description> Love the Paradise Nature Reserve Walk.
Playing TT under the reviving tree with the spring golden dusk. How beautiful!</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 013</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt13/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt13/</guid><description> Old bat vs shield today!</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 012</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt12/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt12/</guid><description> Tangled in many documents&amp;hellip;I did not managed doing much productive work!
At least I wrote TT in Chinese/Mandarin today.</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 011</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt11/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt11/</guid><description> Biking to outdoor Tai Chi practice with a TT ball was great!</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 010</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt10/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt10/</guid><description> I dug out my ancient beloved bat, purchased from a shop run by a lady TT player in Singapore 14 years ago, went through 3 Varsities and many league matches, followed by a long term rest when I ended my student life finishing the PhD&amp;hellip;
Um&amp;hellip; could do with a bit of glue and A New Match!</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 009</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt9/</guid><description> I love to teach preschool and primary school children. They often surprise me with their answers and questions.
When I asked a group of children what can you find in spring: &amp;ldquo;flowers&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;birds&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;green trees&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;bees&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; the youngest kid answered shyly &amp;ldquo;new life&amp;rdquo;.
I went to find the &amp;ldquo;new life&amp;rdquo; in the garden with my TT ball for a picture.</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 008</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt8/</guid><description> It was a beautiful morning. I walked to probably the highest point of land in Cambridge.</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 007</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt7/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt7/</guid><description>Temperature showed as -1°C, we cycled out at 07:40 this morning to catch our first swimming lessons since the pandemic started. Cycling through the frosty grass land, the wind through the gaps of my bike helmet brought a chill.
The pool was full of energy and excitement. We were so glad that we caught the lessons and I even remembered the TT ball for a photo at the end!</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 006</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt6/</guid><description> One of the reasons I love Cambridge - so many directions you could choose to go!</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 005</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt5/</guid><description> We enjoyed 2 days of British summer then there was snow! Early buds had frostbite. It reminded me of childhood frostbite at the bamboo forest village, my first home where people are working their hardest to catch fresh tea leaf buds. Quality and quantity rely mainly on the weather.
Life is unpredictable, life is hard, life is beautiful!</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 004</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt4/</guid><description> Saw a couple were playing TT with the beautiful sunset. I did a walk yesterday morning via the site bringing along a TT ball for the photo.
Typical, I rushed back into my walk and left the ball with the tree. 40 mins later I found it. Lovely!</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 003</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt3/</guid><description> Took a walk with my sunshine but typical&amp;hellip; I forgot the TT ball that I was planning to take along! So I took the 2nd photo with the ball, the card my 4 year old son made together with the book - Table Tennis The Early Years - previously owned by Simon.</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 002</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt2/</guid><description> Egg &amp;amp; Spoon race!
It was windy at the park, very easy to drop the table tennis balls.
Tried other options.
Easter chocolate eggs were great for the race as well as for the prizes!</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 001</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt1/</guid><description> Lazied around for the Sunday morning, I kicked myself outside for a run.
Ran with my CUTTC hoodie on, please ignore the stains. It is very old! Thumb up post run feeling great. 4.82 km, 25:48.</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - One task a day Table Tennis (1tadTT)</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/table_tennis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/table_tennis/</guid><description>I wish to start and lead an event among the current and past CUTTC members in memory of Professor Simon Maddrell: CUTTC - 1tadTT: 1 Task A Day Table Tennis for 6 months: 10/04 - 09/10/2021 across Simon&amp;rsquo;s 1st anniversary on 10/09/2021. To play a game with some one, to do a jog with a TT ball, or carrying a TT bat to get a coffee&amp;hellip; all counts!
You may find out more information about Simon here:</description></item><item><title>Cancer Research UK Fundraising</title><link>https://yudanren.com/post/2021/01/31/cancer-research-uk-fundraising/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/post/2021/01/31/cancer-research-uk-fundraising/</guid><description>Click to Donate Dear my colleagues, friends and family,
It took me nearly 16 years to arrive at 2021 to talk about my family crisis when I lost my mum from Breast Cancer on 5th February 2005, then 8th April my dad passed away from Colon Cancer post their initial diagnosis as late stage cancers in 2003.
On 5th Feb 2021, I had a “Head Shave” in memory of my parents, particularly my mum when she lost her hair due to the chemo/radio therapies.</description></item><item><title>About Yudan Ren</title><link>https://yudanren.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/about/</guid><description> contact@yudanren.com Visit my LinkedIn Profile.</description></item><item><title>Publications</title><link>https://yudanren.com/publications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/publications/</guid><description>Ren, Y., Crump, C. M., Mackley, M. M., Li Puma, G. and Reis, N. M. (2016). Photo inactivation of virus particles in microfluidic capillary systems. Biotechnol. Bioeng., 113: 1481-1492. doi:10.1002/bit.25912 Ren, Y., Bell, S., Zenner, H. L., Lau, K., Crump, C. M. (2012). Glycoprotein M is important for the efficient incorporation of glycoprotein H-L into herpes simplex virus type 1 particles. J. Gen. Virol., 93: 319-329.</description></item><item><title>遇见</title><link>https://yudanren.com/post/1/01/01/%E9%81%87%E8%A7%81/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/post/1/01/01/%E9%81%87%E8%A7%81/</guid><description>于山 2019年3月 于英国剑桥大学罗宾申学院
一早起床，本想再次披星戴月地离开。勉强蹑手蹑脚地洗漱完毕，弟弟半睡半醒地开始叫“妈妈”，随之哥哥也醒了。我感到实在不能就此和孩子们说“再见”，耐着心地满足了弟弟母乳的要求，然后开开心心地给孩子们准备早餐，陪伴着他们享用的同时匆匆忙忙地吃完了自己的早餐，见缝插针地安排了今天的晚饭，没来得及翻开弟弟拿到妈妈跟前的一本故事书……墙上的钟嘀嘀嗒嗒地走过，眼看着自己的时间变得越来越短。在早餐的末尾，交班给爸爸，一个“再见”，两个香吻，我紧赶慢赶地出发了。
沿着安静的小径穿过罗宾申的花园，一个转弯，我惊喜地看到了一只七彩山鸡！它站在大片的草坪中央，拖着长长的尾羽，圆滚滚的身体雄赳赳的样子。它也扭头看着我快步走过，泰然自若。顿时，我想起了刚刚来到剑桥大学攻读博士不久，在罗宾申学生宿舍后面的那片草坪上，第一次看到这样的山鸡。我隔着玻璃窗远远地望着它，非常激动，激动地想把这个消息告诉远在国内的哥哥，告诉他：我在剑桥看到了和爸爸当年养过的、一摸一样的山鸡了！
我看到它安静地走开了，离开了我的视线，马上冲出屋子去后院的草坪，似乎是想再看一眼，但已找不到它的踪影……我有点失落地回到房间，心情还是激动的。多么美丽的、不曾期待的遇见啊！感恩遇见，似乎完全是偶然的，也似乎有冥冥中的安排。
这也让我想起了开始攻读博士的那个时候，我下定了决心想在三年内攻下学位。第一天去实验室，导师得知我的目标后说，三年很有难度，我们系里面曾经有一个学生在三年内提交了毕业论文，人家还是英语母语的。我听了，没有接话，凭着自己的实际行动跃跃欲试。开学不久后，我自告奋勇地在罗宾申学院做学术讲座，操着非常不熟练的英语，给大家介绍自己熟悉的生物医学研究领域的历史、近况以及展望。人生第一次英语学术讲座，心情非常紧张，在讲座结束以后我才完全打消“后悔自告奋勇”了的心情，听众们让我感到了被大家认同和赞赏的快乐，让我意识到语言的拙劣并不是阻碍交流的最重要因素。那是一场我将此生铭记的遇见。
还记得有一次，检测病毒在宿主细胞里生长曲线的实验，需要在连续20个小时中每隔2-4个小时取样。我计划赶在四点钟的时候开始计时，凌晨三点半起床，骑车直奔实验室的我，顺着罗宾申学院外周的马路，一个急转弯，差点没撞上一头小麂！虽然我们立即分道扬镳，我骑我的单车继续前行，它过它的马路钻近了对面的灌木丛，我俩都吓了一大跳！于小麂，在它的生活习性里，不会预料到在那样的凌晨，会有人悄悄地、快速地骑着单车出现在马路上。于我，剑桥居然有小麂！“对不起小麂，把你吓了一大跳；谢谢你小麂，你是我看到的别样风景。”
此后，我开始慢慢享受给各路听众们介绍、分享自己的研究工作；我再也没有在剑桥看到过小麂；而每当看到山鸡，我激动依然。不论是隔着一片草坪，还是一段马路，还是一条河，一堵围墙……似乎在我和它之间的空气中充斥了一份漂洋过海的心情，浓浓的，淡淡的，看不见摸不着地感受在心里。“小山，你想念你的爸爸了吗？我来轻轻地看看你，我会轻轻地离开。”
感恩遇见。</description></item></channel></rss>