<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tadtts on Virologist</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/</link><description>Recent content in Tadtts on Virologist</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yudanren.com/tadtt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 009</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt9/</guid><description> I love to teach preschool and primary school children. They often surprise me with their answers and questions.
When I asked a group of children what can you find in spring: &amp;ldquo;flowers&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;birds&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;green trees&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;bees&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; the youngest kid answered shyly &amp;ldquo;new life&amp;rdquo;.
I went to find the &amp;ldquo;new life&amp;rdquo; in the garden with my TT ball for a picture.</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 008</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt8/</guid><description> It was a beautiful morning. I walked to probably the highest point of land in Cambridge.</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 007</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt7/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt7/</guid><description>Temperature showed as -1°C, we cycled out at 07:40 this morning to catch our first swimming lessons since the pandemic started. Cycling through the frosty grass land, the wind through the gaps of my bike helmet brought a chill.
The pool was full of energy and excitement. We were so glad that we caught the lessons and I even remembered the TT ball for a photo at the end!</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 006</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt6/</guid><description> One of the reasons I love Cambridge - so many directions you could choose to go!</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 005</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt5/</guid><description> We enjoyed 2 days of British summer then there was snow! Early buds had frostbite. It reminded me of childhood frostbite at the bamboo forest village, my first home where people are working their hardest to catch fresh tea leaf buds. Quality and quantity rely mainly on the weather.
Life is unpredictable, life is hard, life is beautiful!</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 004</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt4/</guid><description> Saw a couple were playing TT with the beautiful sunset. I did a walk yesterday morning via the site bringing along a TT ball for the photo.
Typical, I rushed back into my walk and left the ball with the tree. 40 mins later I found it. Lovely!</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 003</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt3/</guid><description> Took a walk with my sunshine but typical&amp;hellip; I forgot the TT ball that I was planning to take along! So I took the 2nd photo with the ball, the card my 4 year old son made together with the book - Table Tennis The Early Years - previously owned by Simon.</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 002</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt2/</guid><description> Egg &amp;amp; Spoon race!
It was windy at the park, very easy to drop the table tennis balls.
Tried other options.
Easter chocolate eggs were great for the race as well as for the prizes!</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - 1tadTT - Day 001</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/onetadtt1/</guid><description> Lazied around for the Sunday morning, I kicked myself outside for a run.
Ran with my CUTTC hoodie on, please ignore the stains. It is very old! Thumb up post run feeling great. 4.82 km, 25:48.</description></item><item><title>CUTTC - One task a day Table Tennis (1tadTT)</title><link>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/table_tennis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yudanren.com/tadtt/table_tennis/</guid><description>I wish to start and lead an event among the current and past CUTTC members in memory of Professor Simon Maddrell: CUTTC - 1tadTT: 1 Task A Day Table Tennis for 6 months: 10/04 - 09/10/2021 across Simon&amp;rsquo;s 1st anniversary on 10/09/2021. To play a game with some one, to do a jog with a TT ball, or carrying a TT bat to get a coffee&amp;hellip; all counts!
You may find out more information about Simon here:</description></item></channel></rss>